2threads.com 2010-04-02

# Privacy Policy : 2threads - A social network with style - fashion events, photos, interviews, shopping, community

## Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy

2threads.com ("2THREADS")   
Terms & Conditions of 2THREADS Website  
ABN: 50 127 257 907  
Company: 2 threads Pty Ltd  
Last updated 27th August 2008

**

This statement outlines how we use your personal information, including information collection and usage. 

2threads respects your personal privacy and we want your on-line experience with us to be as enjoyable as possible. In order to fulfill this, we operate our collection of your personal information under strict guidelines. The types of information we collect are personal contact information (emails addresses, postal addresses, phone numbers etc), financial information (credit card details), profile information (age, status, occupation etc), communication messages (messages within the system), usage information and information associated with the shopping functionality of the website. 

We use your personal contact information that you provide in the sign up process to contact you about our services, notify you of content uploads, and to send you newsletters. Your personal information will not be posted on the website, hired, sold or distributed in anyway to any external 3rd parties that are not part of the 2threads Pty Ltd business or are not an approved partner of 2 threads Pty Ltd, unless required by law. You can change and update your personal contact information at any time when logged into your profile. You can also unsubscribe to notification emails and newsletters at any time. 

Your profile information is provided by you and posted for all members and non-members to see on your profile page in order to improve your interaction with other members of the website. You have the option of not providing this information at all should you choose to, this can be done through your profile page. It is your responsibility to control this information and be aware that is viewable by the public and all 2threads.com members. 

Your Communication Messages information is your private information and we do not access or read these message at anytime, unless required to by law or if in a special case where a user is breaking the terms of our user agreement. Your communication messages will not be made available to any 3rd parties at any time that are not part of the 2threads.com business unless required by law. 

We collect usage information including statistics on how our users are moving around the website and interacting with certain parts of the website through cookies and other measures. We collect this information so we can learn about our user‘s movements and in turn improve the 2threads.com website for all members. We will occasionally share this information with 3rd parties so they can also learn how our users interact with the website. This information however will never be mixed with your personal information and will only be reviewed as a whole and not on an individual level. 

It is always your responsibility to keep your password information private and not pass it onto any 3rd parties. We take no responsibility for any actions that arise for you not abiding by this term. We will never share your password or login information with an 3rd parties under any circumstances unless required by law. 

We reserve the right to change or amend this privacy policy at any time. It is your responsibility to stay updated with these changes through the link to this privacy policy on our website. 

If you wish to update any forms of your information at ay time or subscribe from any notifications or newsletter you can do so through your profile page or the unsubscribe links in our newsletters. 

If you require any further assistance or would like to discuss our privacy policy with us please email [feedback@2threads.com](mailto:feedback@2threads.com)
